Guide to the Elizabeth Page Harris Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Printed Works, 1881-1959; Series VI; 3.0' (8 boxes)
  - Shorter works
    - Delafield, Maturin L. William Smith, 1881 (Box 113, Folder 2270)
    - Fales, Walter. "Phenomenology of Questions", 1943 (Box 113, Folder 2271)
    - Faris, John T., ed. Intermediate Pupil's Quarterly, 1922 (Box 114, Folder 2272)
    - First Fruits, 1956 (Box 114, Folder 2273)
    - Fleet's Review, 1930-1931 (Box 114, Folder 2274-2275)
    - Fort Hall Centennial (official program), 1934 (Box 114, Folder 2276)
    - Frost, Robert. "The Wood Pile", 1961 (Box 114, Folder 2277)
    - Gardening pamphlets, 1935-1942 (Box 114, Folder 2278)
    - Getting Acquainted with Marble, 1937 (Box 114, Folder 2279)
    - Gilmore, M. T. Alaska in Summer: A Daily Record, undated (Box 114, Folder 2280)
    - Good Housekeeping, 1908 November (Box 114, Folder 2281)
    - Handbook of the Department of Decorative Arts of Eutope and America, 1928 (Box 114, Folder 2282)
    - Handbook of the Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1916 (Box 114, Folder 2283)
    - The Hispanic Society of America, 1937, undated (Box 114, Folder 2284)
    - Hoeber, Paul B. Medical Publications and Importations, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 2285)
    - Indexing and filing pamphlets, 1932, 1938 (Box 114, Folder 2286)
    - Industry's Program for American Progress 1939, 1938 (Box 114, Folder 2287)
    - Instruction booklets, 1908, undated (Box 114, Folder 2288)
    - International Friendship in the Church: Programs and Methods, 1917 (Box 114, Folder 2289)
    - Irwin, Will. Hoover as an Executive, 1920 (Box 114, Folder 2290)
    - Knight, Marietta. A Primer of Essentials in Grammar and Rhetoric, 1905 (Box 114, Folder 2291)
    - Lights of Turrell: A Credit Union Lights the Way to a Better Life, 1944 (Box 114, Folder 2292)
    - Los Angeles Guide, 1938 May (Box 114, Folder 2293)
    - Magazine articles, 1918, undated (Box 114, Folder 2294)
    - Magazine fiction, 1899, undated (Box 114, Folder 2295)
    - Magazine fiction, 1911-1915, undated (Box 115, Folder 2296-2302)
    - Making Cellars Dry, 1938 (Box 115, Folder 2303)
    - Mobley, Milly Lou. Me Spik English, 1938 (Box 115, Folder 2304)
    - National Geographic Society maps, 1924-1941 (Box 115, Folder 2305)
    - Nesbitt, Florence. The Chicago Standard Budget for Dependent Families, 1919 (Box 115, Folder 2306)
    - Old Concord, undated (Box 115, Folder 2307)
    - Old Favorite Songs, undated (Box 115, Folder 2308)
    - Pennsylvania Public Instruction, 1942 January (Box 115, Folder 2309)
    - A Philosophy of Higher Education, 1944 (Box 115, Folder 2310)
    - The Province of Carolina, 1944 (Box 115, Folder 2311)
    - Religious pamphlets, undated (Box 115, Folder 2312)
    - Robinson, W. W. The Island of Santa Catalina, 1941 (Box 115, Folder 2313)
    - The Romance of the Smithsonian Institution, 1942 (Box 115, Folder 2314)
    - "Rug Lore", undated (Box 115, Folder 2315)
    - Santa Barbara County California, 1915 (Box 115, Folder 2316)
    - The Saturday Review of Literature, 1926 (Box 115, Folder 2317)
    - The Shield, 1947 (Box 115, Folder 2318)
    - Snyder and McDermott. The Short Circuit, undated (Box 115, Folder 2319)
    - The Story of Edmonton School District No. 7, 1935 (Box 115, Folder 2320)
    - The Susqui-Centennial International Exposition, 1926 (Box 115, Folder 2321)
    - The Unicorn Tapestries, 1938 (Box 116, Folder 2322)
    - Unitarian News Letter, 1930 December (Box 116, Folder 2323)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture. Shall I Be a Farmer?, 1944 (Box 116, Folder 2324)
    - A Visitor's Guide to the Riverside Church, undated (Box 116, Folder 2325)
    - W., L. H. The Little Child's Catechism, undated (Box 116, Folder 2326)
    - Waln, Nora. "Marching Through the Mulberries", 1939 (Box 116, Folder 2327)
    - Williams, M. B. Jasper Trails, undated (Box 116, Folder 2328)
    - The Work of the Merrymount Press, 1942 (Box 116, Folder 2329)
    - Wyoming: Worth Knowing, undated (Box 116, Folder 2330)
- Photographs, 1892-1967; Series VII; 5.0' (11 boxes)
  Series VII, PHOTOGRAPHS, has four alphabetically arranged sections: People (Boxes 117-1120), Albums (Boxes 120-121), Places (Boxes 122-124), and Oversize (Boxes 125-127). A folio of additional oversize material is also included in the series.
  - People
    - Brate, Charlotte, undated (Box 117, Folder 2331)
    - Brokaw, Arthur, 1904 (Box 117, Folder 2332)
    - Celebrities, 1907, undated (Box 117, Folder 2333)
    - Darling, Margaret, 1916, 1918 (Box 117, Folder 2334)
    - Dewey, Emma Rider and Frank A. Dewey, 1910, undated (Box 117, Folder 2335)
    - Downe, Edward, undated (Box 117, Folder 2336)
    - Friends and relatives, 1879-1961, undated (Box 117, Folder 2337)
    - Guilbert, Horace Moss, Circa 1917 (Box 117, Folder 2338)
    - Harris family, 1928-1952, undated (Box 117, Folder 2339-2340)
    - Harris, Elizabeth Merwin Page, 1899-1962, undated (Box 117, Folder 2341-2355)
      See also: Box 126, folders 2488-2890
    - Harris, Herbert Taylor, 1954-1955 (Box 117, Folder 2356)
    - Harris, Herbert Taylor, 1954-1959, undated (Box 118, Folder 2357-2361)
    - Japanese relocation, 1942 (Box 118, Folder 2362)
    - Keeter, Mary Elizabeth ("Bee"), 1921-1923 (Box 118, Folder 2363)
    - Kellogg, Theodora, 1899, 1902, undated (Box 118, Folder 2364-2365)
    - Lyman family, 1951-1963 (Box 118, Folder 2366-2371)
    - Merritt, Edith A., 1949-1958, undated (Box 118, Folder 2372-2373)
    - Merritt, Mrs., undated (Box 118, Folder 2374)
    - Oklahoma friends and missions, 1931, 1949, undated (Box 118, Folder 2375-2376)
    - Page family, undated (Box 118, Folder 2377)
    - Page, Alfred Rider, undated (Box 118, Folder 2378)
      See also: Box 127, folder, 2498
    - Page, Angeline Rider, undated (Box 119, Folder 2379)
    - Page, Elizabeth Merwin Roe, undated (Box 119, Folder 2380)
    - Rider, Richard Price, 1909 (Box 119, Folder 2381)
    - Roberts, John Randall, Jr., undated (Box 119, Folder 2382)
    - Roe family, undated (Box 119, Folder 2383-2386)
    - Roe, Caroline Marsh, undated (Box 119, Folder 2387-2388)
    - Roe, Joseph Wickham, 1918, undated (Box 119, Folder 2389)
    - Roe, Mary Sherwood Lambertson, 1959, undated (Box 119, Folder 2390)
    - Roe, Walter Clark and Mary Wickham Roe, undated (Box 119, Folder 2391)
    - Schauffler family, 1921-1960, undated (Box 119, Folder 2392-2399)
    - Schauffler, Marjorie Page, 1919, undated (Box 119, Folder 2400)
    - Schauffler, Peter Page and family, 1957, 1967, undated (Box 119, Folder 2401)
    - Schauffler, Richard Manvel and Winifred Schauffler Neil, Circa 1922 (Box 120, Folder 2402)
    - Schauffler, Richard Manvel and family, 1952-1957, undated (Box 120, Folder 2403-2404)
    - Stirling, Dorothy, undated (Box 120, Folder 2405)
    - Tallant, Edith, 1918, undated (Box 120, Folder 2406)
    - Tompkins, Stuart and Edna Tompkins, undated (Box 120, Folder 2407)
    - Vannier, Marion L., 1949-1955, undated (Box 120, Folder 2408)
    - Vassar College reunions, 1962-1967 (Box 120, Folder 2409)
    - Wickham, Elizabeth Merwin, 1892 (Box 120, Folder 2410)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 120, Folder 2411-2415)
  - Albums
    - California home of Caroline Marsh Roe, undated (Box 120, Folder 2416)
    - "Ye Kodak Book" (Theodora Kellogg), 1916 (Box 120, Folder 2417)
    - "The Lark's Nest" (Theodora Kellogg), 1916 (Box 120, Folder 2418)
    - Mohonk Lodge, 1912 (Box 120, Folder 2419)
    - Memorabilia removed from album, 1915, undated (Box 121, Folder 2420)
    - Pictures removed from album, Circa 1912-1917 (Box 121, Folder 2421)
    - Page family, undated (Box 121, Folder 2422)
    - Schauffler children, Circa 1923-1924 (Box 121, Folder 2423)
    - "Ye Vacation Book" (Theodora Kellogg), 1914-1923, undated (Box 121, Folder 2424)
  - Places
    - Barred Islands, Maine, 1954, undated (Box 122, Folder 2425)
    - Berlin, Germany, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 2426)
    - Brazil, Circa 1931 (Box 122, Folder 2427)
    - California, 1933, undated (Box 122, Folder 2428)
    - California trip (with Edith Tallant), 1953 (Box 122, Folder 2429)
    - Hawaii, 1939 (Box 122, Folder 2430)
    - Jamaica, 1926-1927 (Box 122, Folder 2431)
    - Japan, undated (Box 122, Folder 2432)
    - Lake Bomoseen, Vermont, undated (Box 122, Folder 2433-2434)
    - Manchester, Vermont, 1902-1939, undated (Box 122, Folder 2435)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 122, Folder 2436)
    - New York State, undated (Box 122, Folder 2437)
    - New Zealand, undated (Box 122, Folder 2438)
    - Postcards
      - Arizona, undated (Box 122, Folder 2439)
      - Auburn, New York, undated (Box 122, Folder 2440)
      - Battle of Wyoming, 1778, undated (Box 122, Folder 2441)
      - British Columbia, undated (Box 122, Folder 2442)
      - California, 1918, undated (Box 122, Folder 2443)
      - Carlinville, Illinois, undated (Box 122, Folder 2444)
      - The Cloisters, New York City, undated (Box 122, Folder 2445)
      - Fraunces Tavern, New York City, undated (Box 122, Folder 2446)
      - Free Library of Philadelphia, undated (Box 122, Folder 2447)
      - Great Britain, undated (Box 122, Folder 2448)
      - Lebanon, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 2449)
      - Louisiana, undated (Box 122, Folder 2450)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York City, undated (Box 123, Folder 2451)
      - Mexico, undated (Box 123, Folder 2452)
      - Museum of the City of New York, undated (Box 123, Folder 2453)
      - New Jersey, undated (Box 123, Folder 2454)
      - New York City, undated (Box 123, Folder 2455)
      - New York State, 1921, undated (Box 123, Folder 2456-2457)
      - Pennsylvania, undated (Box 123, Folder 2458)
      - Southern states, undated (Box 123, Folder 2459)
      - United States, undated (Box 123, Folder 2460)
      - Vassar College, undated (Box 123, Folder 2461)
      - Western states, undated (Box 123, Folder 2462)
    - Sierra Madre, California, Circa 1933 (Box 123, Folder 2463)
    - "Sunny-Side", undated (Box 123, Folder 2464)
    - Unidentified places, 1942-1962, undated (Box 123, Folder 2465-2466)
    - United States, undated (Box 123, Folder 2467)
    - Vassar College, undated (Box 123, Folder 2468)
    - Vermont, undated (Box 123, Folder 2469-2470)
    - Walnut Hill School, 1914-1915 (Box 123, Folder 2471)
    - Western trip (with Caroline Marsh Roe), Circa 1915 (Box 123, Folder 2472)
    - Western trip (with Anna Burton), 1927 (Box 123, Folder 2473)
    - Western trip (with Anna Burton), 1927 (Box 124, Folder 2474)
    - Western trips, 1933, undated (Box 124, Folder 2475-2478)
    - Wisconsin, undated (Box 124, Folder 2479)
    - World, undated (Box 124, Folder 2480)
    - World trip, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 2481)
    - Wyoming, 1947, undated (Box 124, Folder 2482-2484)
  - Oversize
    - Rolled photographs, 1919, undated (Box 125, Folder 2485)
    - American Red Cross nurses, undated (Box 126, Folder 2486)
    - Grand Canyon, undated (Box 126, Folder 2487)
    - Harris, Elizabeth Merwin Page, 1942, 1962, undated (Box 126, Folder 2488-2490)
    - Page, Elizabeth Merwin Roe?, undated (Box 126, Folder 2491)
    - 1914 (Box 126, Folder 2492)
    - Roe, Mary Wickham, undated (Box 126, Folder 2493)
    - Album: Western scenes, 1922 (Box 126, Folder 2494)
    - Downe, Helen, undated (Box 127, Folder 2495)
    - Harris, Elizabeth Merwin Page: Miss Schoonmaker's School, undated (Box 127, Folder 2496)
    - "The Howards of Virginia": Press Book, 1940 (Box 127, Folder 2497)
    - Page, Alfred Rider, 1908 (Box 127, Folder 2498)
    - Schauffler, Bennet and Marjorie Page: wedding picture, 1920 (Box 127, Folder 2499)
    - Unidentified females, undated (Box 127, Folder 2500)
    - Unidentified males, undated (Box 127, Folder 2501-2502)
    - Wyoming Speaks in Pictures, undated (Box 127, Folder 2503)
    - Bordeaux Embarkation Camp, 1918 (Box 127A)
    - Camp Fire Girls, 1921-1922 (Box 127A)
    - Diplomas and certificates, 1907-1918 (Box 127A)
    - Schauffler, Marjorie Page: diploma, 1915 (Box 127A)
    - Newspaper clippings of Vassar College, 1915 (Box 127A)
    - Wickham, Roe, and Page families, undated (Box 127A)
    - Harris, Elizabeth Merwin Page, undated (Box 127A)
- Additional Material, 1903-1968; 0.5' (1 box)
  The ADDITION to the Harris Papers contains twenty-five folders of chronological correspondence and two folders of other material.
  - Correspondence, 1903-1968, undated (Box 128, Folder 2504-2528)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 128, Folder 2529)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 128, Folder 2530)